mergemedia.net 2014-03-05

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy and Disclaimer**  
MergeMedia Corp operates mergemedia.com, which is an Internet portal site and has links to external sites. MergeMedia is not responsible for the contents of these sites, and does not operate them. We provide information and reviews on our site for the convenience of our visitors and these articles are written to the best of our knowledge and editorial guidelines. We cannot be held responsible for any of these descriptions.

**Collecting Data**  
MergeMedia only collects your name and email address with your consent to join our newsletter. We will also log your IP,and the time/date in which you signed up in order to prevent abuse. We do not collect any other personal information at this point of time.

**Sharing Data**  
MergeMedia does not disclose your personal information to any third parties.

**Statistical Analysis**  
MergeMedia does keep track of the pages you surf to and your user preferences, but we only view the data as a form of statistical analysis. We do not view individual surfing styles of users.

**Copyrights and Trademarks**  
All the trademarks and copyrights on this site are the property of the respective owners, and have to the best of our knowledge, been used with permission. Most of the promotional offers listed on mergemedia.com are from various sites around the Internet, and we do our best to ensure trademark and copyright compliance. If there are any discrepancies, please contact our support desk.

**Visitor Comments**  
Visitors are permitted to post comments on MergeMedia on each page and article, and these comments obviously reflect the opinions of the visitor who posted them, and are not endorsed by MergeMedia, and may not reflect the views of MergeMedia. Your mileage may vary.

**Is it REALLY Free?!**  
Some of the Advertismenet on our site are not 100% free. You may have to pay Shipping or handling fees or be subjected to other conditions to get some free items. When you are giving out your personal information, please **read their privacy policy and all details first.**

**State and Local Laws**  
If any of the web-sites which are listed on MergeMedia, contain offers which are prohibited by a state or local law which affects you, We insist that you consider the offers null and void, and you should not participate. It is your responsibility to know your state and local laws.

MergeMedia has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our business in the highest ethical standards and to uphold our promise to the public. However, our policy might change periodically, due to the changes within the environment.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on mergemedia.com send directly to your browsers. 

They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Adsense privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

MergeMedia has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. mergemedia.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Still need help or have questions?**  

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://mergemedia.com/contact.html) anytime.

##### Most Popular Related Articles

  *  Backjoy Seat Topper Sit Without Back Pain
  *  My Web Face Toolbar Make Yourself into a Cartoon
  *  Fling.com Adult Personals
  *  Publishers Clearing House Super Prize
  *  Hot Topic Music Inspired Clothing
  *  Free Cosmo Subscription
  *  Fingerhut.com
  *  SinglesNet Online Dating
  *  Real Mature Singles Over 50
  *  Thirty Plus Singles Quick Sign Up

##### Recently Posted Related Articles
